<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>In Pursuit of Delivering Happiness</title><link>https://mmorozkov.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on In Pursuit of Delivering Happiness</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mmorozkov.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Delivering Happiness Book Review</title><link>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/book-review/delivering-happiness/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/book-review/delivering-happiness/</guid><description>I’ve been contemplating the idea of reading this book for years. It’s actually been so long on the reading list, so that I don’t even remember how it ended up there, who recommended it and why I thought it was worthwhile reading it. Luckily, folks in our internal engineering reading club asked to switch gears and read/discuss something less technical, so I offered a several books off the top of my list.</description></item><item><title>Tailoring Hiring Process</title><link>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/hiring/hiring-process/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/hiring/hiring-process/</guid><description>This write up aims to provide meaningful tips and guidelines for tailoring your hiring routine. It&amp;rsquo;s based on my experience working in mid-size outsourcing company and best advice I could find on the internet.
Most organization have their established ad-hoc processes, thus it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the basics. Recruitment process seems insidously easy: just hop on a call to talk to a candidate. However, most of the work that increases the quality of the outcomes is done behind the scenes in preparation, precise decision making policy and actionable feedback.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://mmorozkov.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmorozkov.github.io/about/</guid><description>I am a manager with a solid engineering background: last 15+ years I spent either writing software or helping tech teams do so. Transition into management is usually a bumpy road, but to me it proved to be a blessing, as I enjoy working with my teams and getting things done together as never before, and it also pays back with never-ending source of unique puzzles.
I am currently working as a Head of Delivery Unit at Devexperts from my home office in St.</description></item></channel></rss>