<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on In Pursuit of Delivering Happiness</title><link>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on In Pursuit of Delivering Happiness</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Matrix Has You</title><link>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/privacy/matrix-has-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/privacy/matrix-has-you/</guid><description>I recently bought a new TV, and when I was setting it up, it prompted me to download an app to finish the installation, which already sounded awkward. But the was just a beginning: I could not expect that app would say that in order to continue finishing the installation of my TV, I needed to grant it full access to my location ALWAYS. It triggered me so much, and actually made me think how far down the rabbit hole with privacy (or should I say lack thereof) we are already.</description></item><item><title>Metaverse Perspectives</title><link>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/web3/metaverse/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/web3/metaverse/</guid><description>I’ve sat down with colleagues to talk about crypto and NFT, to dissect the concept of Metaverse, its future development and potential downside risks.
This piece initially was posted on Devexperts blog
Fiat → Crypto → Metaverse Link to heading Cryptocurrencies offer a greater set of advantages over fiat currencies. They’re safer and far less strictly regulated. They also have other advantages that made them so popular, like:
Fraud-resistance. Since cryptocurrencies are digital and cannot be revered arbitrarily by the sender, they’re essentially safe from fraud and counterfeiting.</description></item><item><title>Management in Game of Thrones. Season 1</title><link>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/got-management/got-s1-management/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/got-management/got-s1-management/</guid><description>Recently, I caught a cold and was lying in bed with flu symptoms, being bored to death. Who knows why, I decided to rewatch Game of Thrones, and 10 minutes in, I started noticing that I was unwittingly, but inherently spotting how main characters were primarily unable to solve what seemed to be typical management cases they were presented with. As if knowing the plot and each character’s path, led my brain cells to exercise a bit.</description></item><item><title>Delivering Happiness Book Review</title><link>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/book-review/delivering-happiness/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/book-review/delivering-happiness/</guid><description>I’ve been contemplating the idea of reading this book for years. It’s actually been so long on the reading list, so that I don’t even remember how it ended up there, who recommended it and why I thought it was worthwhile reading it. Luckily, folks in our internal engineering reading club asked to switch gears and read/discuss something less technical, so I offered a several books off the top of my list.</description></item><item><title>Tailoring Hiring Process</title><link>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/hiring/hiring-process/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmorozkov.github.io/posts/hiring/hiring-process/</guid><description>This write up aims to provide meaningful tips and guidelines for tailoring your hiring routine. It&amp;rsquo;s based on my experience working in mid-size outsourcing company and best advice I could find on the internet.
Most organization have their established ad-hoc processes, thus it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the basics. Recruitment process seems insidously easy: just hop on a call to talk to a candidate. However, most of the work that increases the quality of the outcomes is done behind the scenes in preparation, precise decision making policy and actionable feedback.</description></item></channel></rss>